ehbsr.com 2018-08-16

# eHBSR

**Home Buyers Marketing II, Inc.  
Privacy Policy & Terms of Use**

## PRIVACY POLICY

**Our Commitment**  
Information about you and your home buying needs and preferences will give HBM II the ability to personalize your search criteria and display selected properties on your _Home Buyers Scouting Report_ ® ( _HBSR_ ) website that match your needs, preferences and financial ability to purchase. When you provide us with such information, you consent to its collection by HBM II, and its use by HBM II, its affiliates, and trusted cooperating businesses as described in this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. Also, if you request HBM II to arrange a home showing for you or provide other additional assistance in your home buying efforts, HBM II may recommend a real estate agent who is available to provide such assistance, and will share your information with that agent. Having this information will help the agent be more responsive to your specific needs and preferences.

Nevertheless, we fully understand that it is important to keep any information we collect from or about you safe and confidential. As described below, when we share information with other parties with your consent, we do so only with parties who have agreed to keep your information confidential. However, you may prohibit our sharing this information by clicking on the "I Decline" button below, although this will result in your not being able to use the features of the _HBSR_ website. You may also terminate our ability to share this information at any time by sending us an e-mail asking to have your account canceled. We will not share the information you provide to us or that we collect from monitoring your use of our password-protected website with any third party except as described in this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.

 **Security Practices Protect Your Information**  
We permit our employees and contractors to access your personal information only when the information is necessary for them to do their jobs. Our employees and contractors who have access to your information are required to protect it and keep it confidential. We use technology to keep your information and transactions private and secure. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality, availability and integrity of your personal information.

 **The Information We Will Collect**  
The only information we will collect from you is:  

  * Basic identification data such as your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address.
  * Your stated preferences as to the characteristics and location of properties in which you are interested.
  * Data about your use of the site that we will use to verify the level of your interest and your preferences.

 **Sharing of information with Third Parties**  
We will share the information we collect only with:  

  * Trusted cooperating businesses who work with HBM II under confidentiality agreements. Our trusted cooperating businesses are businesses that either referred you to us and/or provide a service we believe may be useful to you in the homebuying process. Cooperating businesses do not have any independent right to share your information. Cooperating businesses include the real estate agency and/or mortgage company, as well as their agents and/or loan officers, who may have referred you to us or who are working with you and HBM II. Cooperating businesses may also include providers of other services related to the homebuying process such as a title company or attorney, a home insurer, a home builder, or a moving company.
  * Our non-affiliated service providers such as technical systems consultants and programmers who agree to keep this customer information strictly confidential;
  * Other third parties only to comply with a subpoena or court order, to protect against potential or actual fraud, or to facilitate the work of our auditors. 

**The Information We Will Provide**  
You agree that any property information HBM II provides to you through the HBSR service is only for your personal, non-commercial use as a bona fide prospective buyer of such property, and may not be used commercially or disclosed, copied, retransmitted or distributed to any other person. You acknowledge that any home listing information you obtain through the _HBSR_ service is copyrighted information owned by the Multiple Listing Service or Real Estate Broker that provided the information.

 **Communications**  
You agree that you may receive periodic emails and telephone calls regarding your home buying efforts from HBM II and from , a licensed real estate broker with HBM II with whom you have been in previous contact. HBM II and are providing the _HBSR_ service to you.

You agree that a licensed real estate agent who is cooperating with HBM II and with whom you are working may contact you by email or telephone to further assist you in your home buying efforts.

You agree that if you request HBM II to arrange a home showing for you or provide other additional assistance in your home buying efforts, HBM II may recommend a real estate agent who is available to provide such assistance, and agree that real estate agent may contact you by email or telephone to offer assistance in your home buying efforts.

You agree that with , with whom you have been in previous contact,* may contact you by email or telephone to continue working with you to determine what homes on your _HBSR_ website are within your financial ability to purchase. You agree and request that when you personally select a specific property for inclusion in your _HBSR_ website's favorite properties, HBM II shall inform with of your indication of interest in that specific property so that with can better prepare to be available to assist you in reviewing and/or developing your mortgage financing options on that specific property.

You agree that HBM II's other trusted cooperating businesses may use your information, including your email address, to communicate with you about their service offerings.

##  TERMS OF USE

We acknowledge from your previous communication to us that you desire to initiate further communications with , , and of HBM II. Therefore, as you requested, the _HBSR_ service will display to you the contact information for those persons to facilitate such communication. You also acknowledge and agree that the _HBSR_ service may display to you the contact information of other trusted cooperating businesses offering services that are available to assist your homebuying process, to facilitate your ability to send communications to those businesses if you choose to do so.

We at HBM II sincerely hope you enjoy using the free real estate service we call the _Home Buyers Scouting Report_ ®.

 **Our Relationship**  
Your acceptance of this "Privacy Policy and Terms of Use" imposes no financial obligation on you. By accepting this "Privacy Policy and Terms of Use," you agree you will only use the information you obtain from HBM II for the purposes described above in "The Information We Will Provide." You also agree to the further communications and uses of your information described above in "Our Commitment," "Communications," and "Sharing of Information with Third Parties." You also agree and acknowledge that acceptance of this "Privacy Policy and Terms of Use" does not create any fiduciary duty to you on the part of HBM II and does not create any buyer representation agreement between you and HBM II.

HBM II and its licensed broker agree and acknowledge that your acceptance of this "Privacy Policy and Terms of Use" creates a broker consumer relationship agreement between yourself and HBM II. In this relationship, you are the consumer and is the broker. This broker consumer relationship only imposes on HBM II and the obligations that HBM II expressly assumes in this "Privacy Policy and Terms of Use," together with the obligations that the law imposes on a broker who is assisting a consumer in a broker consumer relationship.

If you have an exclusive representation agreement with any other real estate agent or broker, that agreement may prohibit you from receiving the type of real estate services that HBM II provides through the _HBSR_ service unless you first obtain that agent or broker's permission. By accepting this "Privacy Policy and Terms of Use," you warrant and affirm that you are not in an exclusive representation agreement with another real estate agent or broker that prevents you from now agreeing to receive the _HBSR_ service from HBM II and .

**Trade Secrets.** For the purpose of this Terms of Use, "Trade Secrets" means any information which is proprietary to or owned by HBM II relating to the HBSR, now existing or reasonably foreseeable, whether in a written, electronic, verbal, or other form, and includes, without limitation, the following: (a) all websites designed, created and developed by HBM II or its affiliated companies, including all passwords, text, content, color schemes, images, graphics, information, look and feel, layout, methodology, metrics, graphical interfaces and functionality for each website; (b) information and materials comprising or relating to any current, future or proposed products or services; (c) analyses, factual evaluations and/or summaries of real estate listings, compilations, data bases, studies or other printed or electronic documents prepared by anyone in connection with the review or evaluation of any information developed by or pertaining to HBM II; (d) copyrights, patents, patents pending, electronic records, computer processes, computer systems, computer hardware configurations, software source codes and software owned, developed or acquired by HBM II; and (d) other information relating to HBM II that is not commonly known to persons or other sources outside of HBM, whether or not specifically marked or identified as "confidential" or "trade secret” by HBM II.

 **Limitations on Use of Trade Secrets** You agree that you will not: (a) disclose, reveal, divulge, disseminate or deliver (collectively, "Disclose") any Trade Secrets to any third party; (b) use, utilize, employ, lecture upon, publish, rewrite, reproduce or reverse engineer (collectively, "Use") any Trade Secrets, for your benefit or for the benefit of any other person or entity; or (c) authorize or permit any third person or entity to Disclose or Use any Trade Secrets; 

**Miscellaneous.** If you are found to be in violation of the terms of this Terms of Use, your access to this website may be temporarily or permanently disabled and you may be held liable for all expenses and damages, including court costs and attorneys’ fees, incurred by HBM II, or any of its Affiliated Companies, caused by your failure to abide by the terms and conditions of this Agreement.

You must agree to the Terms of Use set forth herein before you can view listings that match your search criteria on your free _HBSR_ website. By clicking on the "I Accept" button below you (1) agree to the Terms of Use set forth above and (2) authorize us to share the information collected with the real estate broker and loan officer who may have referred you to us and with others as set forth in the Privacy Policy herein.
